Please see the subtitles for more videos.
Next Preview
I'm having a hard time
It's tough, but
I can see that everyone is having a great time
That's why
I want to see everyone's smile
You sound like an idol when you say it like that.
It's very idol-like.
Living together in the modern age
Can you think of a way to do that?
I like muscle training, but I don't like stretching.
I'm not flexible.
What?
You're way beyond that.
You know that, don't you? You.
I'm sure you're comfortable with it.
You're going to look so beautiful when you get there,
I'm just a little careful not to get too excited and rattled when we get to the show.
The set list in the back has a lot of uplifting songs,
So, we have to be calm and keep our goal in mind,
So we have to keep calm and keep our goal in mind.
Maima's routine is like a fluid color,
You know, liquid on liquid.
It's a tame.
I don't like to chew on the day of the concert.
What do you do?
Q. What did you do with the 10 of you?
No, it was great, it was 10 of us.
That's the only thing I'm glad about.
That's the one thing I'm really glad about. From now on,
18 shows?
17?
There are 17 performances,
We will make the most of each one,
Let's build a rhythm!
That's what I'm saying,
What?
Here we go.
Where are we?
Matsumoto!
Go!
Let's go!
Baito!
It's good to be together.
You two, I feel like I can fight for my courage.
Because I want to still love you after 10 years.
You and me.
Yeah, but we're so lucky to have found each other here.
It can't be helped.
So let's be a little more lucky and have a second chance
Let's be together now
I want to tell you something I'm not ashamed of.
Yay!
I'm so tired!
That was so much fun!
It was live!
I'm so tired!